<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GeneralContent</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Kamasutra | Sex Position</string>
   <!-- <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>-->
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Help</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Rate us</string>


    <string name="po_1">Sex Position: Yourself on the Shelf </string>
    <string name="po_2">Sex Position: The Socket</string>
    <string name="po_3">Sex Position: Standing O</string>
    <string name="po_4">Sex Position: The Little Dipper</string>
    <string name="po_5">Sex Position: The 69 Bridge</string>
    <string name="po_6">Sex Position: The Cat </string>
    <string name="po_7">Sex Position: Waterfall </string>
    <string name="po_8">Sex Position: One Up</string>
    <string name="po_9">Sex Position: The Cowgirl </string>
    <string name="po_10">Sex Position: The Hot Seat</string>
    <string name="po_11">Sex Position: Spin Cycle </string>
    <string name="po_12">Sex Position: Stairway to Heaven</string>
    <string name="po_13">Sex Position: Reverse Cowgirl </string>
    <string name="po_14">Sex Position: Pole Position </string>
    <string name="po_15">Sex Position: Face Off</string>

    <string name="po_16">Sex Position: The Lazy Man </string>

    <string name="po_17">Sex Position: David Copperfield </string>
    <string name="po_18">Sex Position: Heir to the Throne</string>
    <string name="po_19">Sex Position: Closed for Business</string>
    <string name="po_20">Sex Position: The Pretzel </string>
    <string name="po_21">Sex Position: The G-Whiz  </string>
    <string name="po_22">Sex Position: Man\'s Best Friend</string>
    <string name="po_23">Sex Position: The Flatiron </string>
    <string name="po_24">Sex Position: Butter Churner </string>
    <string name="po_25">Sex Position: The Ballet Dancer</string>
    <string name="po_26">Sex Position: Stand and Deliver</string>
    <string name="po_27">Sex Position: Iron Chef </string>
    <string name="po_28">Sex Position: H2Ohh Yeah </string>
    <string name="po_29">Sex Position: Wheelbarrow, Standing</string>
    <string name="po_30">Sex Position: Seated Wheelbarrow </string>
    <string name="po_31">Sex Position: The Standing Dragon</string>
    <string name="po_32">Sex Position: Restroom Attendant </string>
    <string name="po_33">Sex Position: Couch Surfer</string>
    <string name="po_34">Sex Position: Quickie-Fix</string>
    <string name="po_35">Sex Position: Mountain Climber</string>
    <string name="po_36">Sex Position: Quicker Picker Upper </string>
    <string name="po_37">Sex Position: Missionary </string>
    <string name="po_38">Sex Position: Spoon</string>
    <string name="po_39">Sex Position: Spork </string>
    <string name="po_40">Sex Position: Gift Wrapped</string>
    <string name="po_41">Sex Position: Spoon, Facing</string>
    <string name="po_42">Sex Position: The X Position </string>
    <string name="po_43">Sex Position: Snow Angel</string>
    <string name="po_44">Sex Position: The Fusion</string>
    <string name="po_45">Sex Position: The Spider</string>
    <string name="po_46">Sex Position: Hovering Butterfly </string>
    <string name="po_47">Sex Position: Sixty Nine </string>
    <string name="po_48">Sex Position: The Face Sitter</string>
    <string name="po_49">Sex Position: The Elevator</string>
    <string name="po_50">Sex Position: Swiss Ball Blitz</string>


    <string name="pos_1" formatted="true">"Sex Position: Yourself on the Shelf\n\n"

"Benefits: It allows for deeper and harder penetration. Also a higher likelihood of orgasming together than other positions.

Technique: Have your partner perch their butt right on the edge of the bed. With you standing in front, you can enter them. Then have them wrap their legs around you. From there, stand up-right, placing your hands around their back to support your partner.

Also Try: If you don’t have the quad and glute muscles to pull this position off, just keep your partner on the edge of the bed, penetrating them there.

Hot Tip: It’s a great way to finish having sex. Since the position is strenuous, try doing it 30-60 seconds before you and your partner are about to orgasm. " </string>
    <string name="pos_2" formatted="true">
        "Benefits: If you're into butts, you'll have a great view.

Technique: From reverse cowgirl, have them bend all the way forward, extending their legs all the way back. They should be supporting their body by resting on their elbows, as if they were holding a plank.

Hot tip: Your partner can easily stimulate their own clitoris while you penetrate them. If the two of you are into spanking, go for it. "</string>
    <string name="pos_3" formatted="true">"Benefits: Ideal position for all things cunnilingus: clit sucking, rubbing, digital penetration, G-spot stimulation.

Technique: While on your knees have your partner stand up-right. They should then drape one of their legs around your shoulder while you eat them out.

Hot tip: Ideally you want your partner's hands above your head. This can be accomplished through the use of some BDSM restraints. If restraints aren’t their thing, see if you can find an anchored bar or beam for them to grasp."</string>
    <string name="pos_4" formatted="false">
       " Benefits: Allows for easy access to both penetrate your partner and stimulate the clitoris manually.

Technique: FYI, the partner on top will have sore triceps once you both finish. For the Little Dipper, the person on top uses either a bed, couch, or chair to hoist themselves over their partner. The person on bottom then inserts his penis into the top’s vagina or anus. The top then does tricep dips to move up and down on their partner’s penis. If done correctly, you should be in a T-shape formation.

Hot tip: Play with the top’s penis or clitoris for extra stimulation. "</string>
    <string name="pos_5" formatted="true">"Also known as: Golden Gate

Technique: This position only works if your mate is particularly flexible and strong. It’s ideal for people who do yoga and are familiar with the pose. A notorious Kama Sutra position, the bridge is a loose variant of the classic 69. While facing towards you, have them “sit on your face,” so to speak, so you’re eating them out. Your mate's legs should be by your side, bent at the knee. From there, have them extender their arms, arch their back, and take you in their mouth.

Hot tip: You may need to help out your by thrusting your pelvis up, so their mouth can actually reach your genitals. "</string>

    <string name="pos_6" formatted="false">"Also known as: Coital Alignment Technique

Benefits: Strong clitoral stimulation. In a study published in the Journal of Sex and Marital Therapy, women who were unable to have an orgasm in the missionary position reported a 56 percent increase in orgasm frequency using the coital alignment technique. Other studies suggest even greater success, with up to 73 percent of women achieving orgasm with CAT.

Technique: The CAT is very similar to the missionary position except your body is positioned farther up and to one side. Instead of being chest to chest, your chest is near your partner's shoulders. Have them bend their legs about 45 degrees to tilt their hips up. This causes the base of your shaft to maintain constant contact with the clitoris.

Also try: Ask your partner to straighten their legs. Push your pelvis down a few inches while they push up.

Hot tip: Instead of thrusting up and down, rock forward and back to (hopefully) provide enough stimulation for your partner to orgasm. Make this position even better by grinding your pelvis in a circular motion."</string>
    <string name="pos_7" formatted="true">"Also known as: Head Rush

Benefits: The blood will rush to your other head too.

Technique: Move to the edge of the bed and lie back with your head and shoulders on the floor as your partner straddles you. The blood will rush to your head creating mind-blowing sensations upon orgasm."</string>
    <string name="pos_8" formatted="false">"Also known as: Over Your Shoulder, The Hamstring Stretch

Benefits: This is the best sex position for people who are particularly sensitive along one side of the clitoris.

Technique: Kneel on the floor with your mate lying on the edge of the bed. Raise one of their legs and ask them to support it by wrapping their hands around their hamstring just below the knee. With one hip raised, your partner will be able to add some movement to aid in your stroking or to help move you to the perfect spot.

Also try: Encourage your partner to wriggle a little to help you get the rhythm right.

Hot tip: During oral sex, allow the knuckle of your finger to trail behind your tongue. The contrast between soft flesh of the tongue and hard bone of the finger will create a pleasing sensation. (For more oral pleasure positions, check out Your Ultimate Guide to Oral Sex.)

Hot tip for her: Your partner can let you know the tongue pressure and technique they prefer by demonstrating with their mouth on your earlobe."</string>
    <string name="pos_9" formatted="true">"Also known as: Woman On Top

Benefits: Puts your mate in control. Great for G-spot stimulation and your partner's orgasm.

Technique: Cowgirl is one of the best sex positions because it allows for a variety of interesting sights and sensations, and offers your partner the psychological advantage of taking charge of pace and depth of penetration. Alternate between shallow and deep thrusts. "Shallow will stimulate the front third of the vagina, which is the most sensitive," says sex therapist Rebecca Rosenblat, author of Seducing Your Man.

Also try: Lie chest to chest, with your partner stretching their legs out on top of your legs. Your partner should brace their feet on the tops of yours and push off to create a rocking motion that will rub the vulva and clitoral area against your pubic bone for greater pleasure.

Hot tip: It will be easier for your partner to climax if you stimulate them manually and orally until they're extremely aroused. From the cowgirl position, have them squat over your face so you can pull off some oral stimulation."</string>
    <string name="pos_10" formatted="false">"Also known as: The Love Seat, The Man Chair

Benefits: Good G-spot stimulation.

Technique: Sit on the edge of the bed or on a chair with your feet on the floor. Your mate turns away and backs up onto you, sitting between your legs. They can ride back and forth by pushing off the chair arms or pressing up with their feet. They can control the angle of entry by arching their back and pressing their buttocks into your groin. While doggy style is about your dominance, The Hot Seat puts your partner in the driver's seat. And that makes it one of the best sex positions for both of you.

Also try: Your partner can reach under and stimulate the base of your penis, scrotum, and perineum. Meanwhile, you can reach around and stimulate their nipples."</string>
    <string name="pos_11" formatted="false">"Also known as: Maytag Repair Man

Benefits: Extra vibes.

Technique: This is a variation on the Hot Seat with your partner sitting in your lap, but this time planting yourselves on top of a washing machine set at the highest agitator cycle."</string>

    <string name="pos_12" formatted="false">"Also known as: Step Lively

Benefits: Good hand holds for your partner, and you don't have to wait until reaching the bedroom.

Technique: This is a variation on the Hot Seat with your partner sitting on top of you while you sit on one of the stairs of a staircase. Stairs offer good seating possibilities, and a hand rail for extra support and lifting leverage for them."</string>
    <string name="pos_13" formatted="true">"Also known as: Rodeo Drive, Half Way Around the World

Benefits: With a pillow under your head, you get an awesome view of your mate's backside. They can control depth of penetration and pace with this sex position.

Technique: Lie on your back with your legs outstretched. Your partner kneels next to you, then turns and spreads their legs, straddling your hips and facing your feet. Kneeling, your partner lowers down onto your penis and begins riding you.

Also try: Have your partner lean forward or back to change the angle of the penis for greater stimulation.

Hot tip for her: From this position, your partner can easily reach down to touch themselves or direct your penis to where it feels best."</string>
    <string name="pos_14" formatted="true">"Also known as: Thighmaster

Benefits: Dual stimulation for your partner; for you—a great view of their rear and your penis entering them.

Technique: Lie on your back and bend one of your legs, keeping the other outstretched. Your partner straddles the raised leg with a thigh on either side and lowers themselves onto your member so that their back is facing you. They should hold your knee and use it for support as they rock up and down.

Also try: They can press their vulva hard against your upper thigh rubbing as the feeling dictates.

Hot tip for her: From Pole Position, your partner can massage your raised leg during the action. Or reach down and touch your perineum."</string>
    <string name="pos_15" formatted="false">"Also known as: The Lap Dance

Benefits: Allows for face-to-face intimacy; cozy for long sessions.

Technique: Sit on a chair or the edge of the bed. Your partner then faces you, wraps their arms around your back, climbs on top, and sits on your lap. Once in the saddle, they can ride up and down on your penis by pressing with their legs or knees. Want to go faster? Assist by grabbing their buttocks and lifting and bouncing.

Also try: Your mate can sit astride facing you on a rocking chair. Old wooden rockers on hardwood or stone floors provide the greatest variety of good vibes.

Hot tip: There's lots of room for creativity in this position for stimulating erogenous areas of the upper body, head, neck, and face. If they like to have their nipples licked, go for it!"</string>
    <string name="pos_16" formatted="false">"Also known as: The Squat Thrust

Benefits: Puts them in control, maintains intimacy.

Technique: Place pillows behind your back and sit on the bed with legs outstretched. Your partner straddles your waist, feet on the bed. They then bends their knees to lower themselves onto you, using one hand to direct your penis in. Just by pressing on the balls of their feet and releasing, they can raise and lower themselves on your shaft as slowly or quickly as they please.

Also try: From this position, you both lie back into the Spider position or its more challenging variation, The X."</string>
    <string name="pos_17" formatted="false">"Also known as: Trick &amp; Treat

Benefits: This sex position is the piece de resistance for partners who prefer a strong, upward stroking motion.

Technique: Place a pillow under their hips to tilt their pelvis up. Bend their knees so they can place their feet on your shoulder blades.

Also try: Amplify your oral efforts with a simple sleight-of-hand trick: While you lap away, try using your hands to push gently upward on their abdomen, stretching their skin away from their pubic bone, and helping to coax the head of the clitoris out from beneath the hood.

Hot tip: Let your tongue rest firmly and flat against the full length of the vaginal entrance, then have them move and grind against your tongue."</string>
    <string name="pos_18" formatted="false">"Also known as: Lazy Girl

Benefits: The ultimate sex position for oral on the go, use this to get your mate in the mood and help them cut loose.

Technique: Have your partner sit on a chair with their legs wide open. You take it from there. This is a good sex position for either beginning the slow build-up with loose, broad, strokes, or ending with strong suction. Your partner is able to easily guide you, and they're able to get a full view of you between her legs, which is a turn-on for many people.

Also try: Switch to a swivel chair and turn it left and right as you hold your tongue stationary.

Hot tip: Insert your index and ring fingers and stroke in a "come hither" motion to wake up their G-spot using this sex position. With either your tongue or other hand, apply pressure to their pubic bone. This dual stimulation executed just right will send your partner over the edge."</string>
    <string name="pos_19" formatted="false">"Benefits: A variation of One Up that allows for slow buildup.

Technique: Some people with vulvas find direct clitoral stimulation uncomfortable. Having your mate close their legs during oral sex may help. Place your hand above their public mound applying light pressure, then rub your firm tongue on the area around the clitoris to add indirect stimulation.

Hot tip: During oral sex allow the knuckle of your index finger of your free hand to trail behind your tongue. The contrast between the soft flesh of the tongue and hard bone of the finger will create a pleasing sensation."</string>
    <string name="pos_20" formatted="false">"Also known as: The Pretzel Dip, The Camel Ride

Benefits: The deep penetration of doggy-style while face to face.

Technique: Kneel and straddle their left leg while they're lying on their left side. Your partner will bend their right leg around the right side of your waist, which will give you access to enter their vagina. For many people with vulvas, rear entry hurts their backs. This sex position allows them to lounge comfortably while enjoying deep penetration.

Also try: Manually stimulate them using your fingers. Or withdraw your penis and, holding the shaft with your left hand, rub the head against their clitoris to bring them to the brink of orgasm. You can reinsert when they want you back inside.

Hot tip: Be gentle with the clitoris. It's more sensitive than your penis, so touch lightly at first. Some people even prefer gentle pressure around it rather than direct stimulation. Go soft, then increase speed and pressure.

Hot tip for her: And ask them to direct you, faster, slower, lighter, harder."</string>

    <string name="pos_21" formatted="false">"Also known as: The Shoulder Holder, The Anvil

Benefits: Allows deep penetration and targeting the G-spot

Technique: Your partner lies on their back. You kneel between their legs and raise them, resting their calves over your shoulders. Rock them in a side-to-side and up-and-down motion to bring the head and shaft of your penis in direct contact with the front wall of their vagina. Because this angle allows for deep penetration, thrust slowly at first avoid causing discomfort.

Also try: Bring their legs down and have them place their feet on your chest in front of your shoulders. This allows your partner to control the tempo and depth of thrusts.

Hot tip: Notice your partner nearing orgasm. You do that by listening for their breath to become short and shallow. Flushed skin and slightly engorged breasts also indicate they're nearing the peak of her arousal."</string>
    <string name="pos_22" formatted="true">"Also known as: Doggy-Style

Benefits: Deep penetration and an erotic view.

Technique: This could be your next move after starting in The Flatiron sex position. Entering your partner from behind, you'll be able to thrust deep so the tip of your penis touches their cervix, an often-neglected pleasure zone. But you should do this slowly and gently. Some people with vulvas find it painful.

Hot tip for her: They may be able to increase the intensity of your orgasm by pushing their pelvic floor muscles outward, as if trying to squeeze something out of their vagina. This causes the vaginal walls to lower, making the G-spot more accessible."</string>

    <string name="pos_23" formatted="true">"Also known as: Downward Dog, The Belly Flop

Benefits: Intensifies vaginal pleasure.

Technique: Your partner lies face down on the bed, knees slightly bent and hips slightly raised. For comfort, and to increase the angle of their hips, they can place a pillow under their lower abs. You enter them from behind and keep your weight off their body by propping yourself up with your arms. This position creates a snug fit, making you feel larger to your partner.

Also try: You'll last longer in this position if you switch to shallower thrusts and begin deep breathing.

Hot tip: Less friction means less stimulation—and can help you last longer. Try using a very slippery silicon-based lubricant, which may allow you to thrust longer before reaching orgasm."</string>
    <string name="pos_24" formatted="true">"Also known as: Squat Thruster

Benefits: An extra rush of blood to your partner's head to increase their ecstasy.

Technique: Have your partner lie on their back with their legs raised over their head. This is not a plain Jane position! Squat over them and dip your penis in and out of them. Be extra careful to thrust lightly to avoid stressing their neck.

Also try: By removing yourself fully, you'll give your partner the extremely pleasurable feeling of you first entering them over and over again.

Hot tip: Novelty ignites passion by increasing your brain's levels of dopamine, a neurotransmitter linked to romance and sex drive, says biological anthropologist Helen Fisher, PhD. The Butter Churner qualifies for novelty, but you don't need to go to such extremes to sustain romance. Anything that's new and different will do the trick."</string>
    <string name="pos_25" formatted="true">"Also known as: Get a Leg Up

Benefits: Erotic move for quickies in tight quarters. Good option for outdoor sex. Allows for easier penetration. Your partner has control of thrusting, depth, and angle.

Technique: You stand facing one another. Your partner raises one of their legs up and wraps it around your buttocks or thigh and pulls you into them with their leg.

Also try: If that wrapped leg gets tired, cradle it with your arm. If your mate's very flexible, lift their leg over your shoulder.

Hot tip: Try this standing position in a hot shower. During the steamy foreplay, rub each other's entire body with a coarse salt scrub to stimulate nerve endings and blood flow."</string>
    <string name="pos_26" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Bicycle

Benefits: You can enjoy the view of your penis thrusting.

Technique: Stand at the edge of a bed or desk while your partner lies back and raises their legs to their chest. Their knees are bent as if they\'re doing a "bicycling" exercise. Grab their ankles and enter them. Thrust slowly, as the deep penetration may be painful for them.

Also try: Have your partner place their heels on your shoulders, which will open their hips so their labia press against you.

Hot tip for her: Encourage your partner to play with their clitoris manually. Also, show them that they can control your penetration by flexing their thighs."</string>
    <string name="pos_27" formatted="true">"Also known as: Kitchen Confidential

Benefits: Good sex position for a quickie with deep penetration.

Technique: A variation of The Ballet Dancer in which your partner raises their legs up and wraps them around your butt or thighs. Your kitchen counter is the perfect height for this standing-to-seated appetizer.
"</string>
    <string name="pos_28" formatted="true">"Also known as: Aquaman\'s Delight

Benefits: Good for an outdoors quickie, while still avoiding prying eyes.

Technique: Another variation of The Ballet Dancer. Your partner\'s buoyancy in the water makes this sex position easier to hold. And all you need to do is shift some bathing suit material out of the way of certain body parts; the lifeguards will be none the wiser."</string>

    <string name="pos_29" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Hoover Maneuver

Benefits: Calorie burner because it\'s so athletic. You can stroll around the house in this position, but draw the shades first.

Technique: You enter your partner as you would in standing, rear entry, but lift them up by the pelvis and have them grip your waist with their legs. Summer camp wheelbarrow races were never this much fun!

Also try: Ask them to rhythmically squeeze their PC muscles to help them climax."</string>

    <string name="pos_30" formatted="true">"Also known as: Wheelbarrow At Rest

Benefits: Less strenuous than the standing varieties of this sex position, while still offering intense sensation.

Also try: Try the wheelbarrow while sitting on the edge of a bed or chair. Movement is limited, but penetration is deep.

Hot tip: Make some noise. Explore the deeper sexual response and energy by letting loose with powerful sounds, a roar, perhaps?"</string>


    <string name="pos_31" formatted="true">"Also known as: Crouching Tiger, Hidden Serpent

Benefits: An ideal position for G-spot stimulation. Seeing the round curves of your partner\'s rear tends to be highly erotic for you.

Technique: Stand and enter your partner from behind as they pose on all fours on the edge of the bed and arch their back to lift their buttocks.

Also try: With your legs outside of theirs, use your thighs to squeeze their knees together, which tightens their vagina around your penis."</string>


    <string name="pos_32" formatted="true">"Also known as: Drop the Soap

Benefits: Good for a quickie at a party.

Technique: Slip into a bathroom and ask them to look into the mirror while you enter them from behind. It lets you have eye contact during the G-spot-targeting rear-entry sex position."</string>


    <string name="pos_33" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Lazy Susan

Benefits: Convenient for a quickie and adds spice outside the bedroom.

Technique: Ask your partner to bend her body over the arm of a couch as you enter them from behind. They can grind on the firm but cushy arm for multiple stimulation with minimal effort.

Also try: Have them cross their ankles. This will squeeze their vaginal and gluteal muscles tightly around your penis."</string>


    <string name="pos_34" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Bends

Benefits: Greater thrusting power, and good for quickie sex in your kitchen, especially if your partner is wearing a skirt.

Technique: Ask them to bend at the waist and rest their hands on a piece of furniture, their knees or the floor for support. You enter them from behind and hold their hips for support as you thrust.

Also try: Reach below to caress their clitoris for extra stimulation.

Hot tip: Massage their shoulders or stimulate their breasts by bending over them."</string>

    <string name="pos_35" formatted="true">"Also" known as: The Pushup

Benefits: Creates great eye-to-eye contact. Keeps your weight off her bod.

Technique: There\'s a reason people swoon when they see a six pack. They know a man with strong abs is going to be great in the sack. The mountain climber position shows off your strength and hard abs (if you have them). While between your partner\'s legs, assume the standard "up" sex position.

Also try: Lower yourself to kiss your partner teasingly while thrusting with your shoulders as well as your pelvis.

Hot tip: Tease them with a series of moves: by entering with just the tip; thrusting just halfway in; then removing yourself and stroking their outside with your member. They can reach down and grab your shaft and rub their clitoris with it."</string>



    <string name="pos_36" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Pillow Driver

Benefits: A little bit of variety if missionary begins to feel stale; good upper body exercise.

Technique: Place a pillow under the small of their back or their buttocks to tilt their pelvis and change the angle of your penetration for different sensations. Bracing yourself with your hands on the bed as in a pushup position, you take your weight off their body."</string>


    <string name="pos_37" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Matrimonial, Male Dominant

Benefits: Lots of eye and body contact.

Technique: The most commonly used position in the world, the missionary is an especially intimate position allowing for face-to-face contact. You like it because you can control penetration depth and speed of thrusting. Your partner enjoys feeling your weight on their body, and the maximum skin-to-skin contact. Note that this position can make it more difficult to hold off ejaculation because of the intense friction and deep thrusting. To lengthen lovemaking, start there then switch to a position that maintains clitoral pressure without so much pelvic back and forth.

Also try: Push up to create space in between you to sneak a small vibrator down for buzzing the top of their mound.

Hot tip: Raise their left leg so their knee is level with your right shoulder. Keep their other leg flat on the bed. Thrust toward the inner thigh of their raised leg. This adjustment forces tighter penetration and more clitoral pressure."</string>


    <string name="pos_38" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Sleeper Hold

Benefits: Comfortable sex position if your partner is pregnant or you\'re heavy. Also ideal for long lovemaking. Good one for falling asleep afterward.

Technique: You both lie on your sides facing the same direction, you in back. Your partner bends their knees and pushes their rear back toward you for easier access to their vagina. Adjusting the lean of your bodies will vary the angle of entry and help with rocking and thrusting.

Also try: Synchronize your breathing. One of you takes the lead and the other follows so that you inhale and exhale together. The coordinated rhythm opens an unspoken dialogue of intimacy.

Hot tip: To give them the sensation of greater width inside them, from the Spoon position have them bend and lift their top leg to their breasts. Adjust your position so you are more on top of them top hip than behind them."</string>



    <string name="pos_39" formatted="true">"Also known as: Spoon and Fork Combo, Scissoring

Benefits: Offers a natural bridge to more creative positions.

Technique: Your partner lies on their back, and raises their right leg so you can position yourself between their legs at a 90-degree angle and enter. Their legs will form the tines of a spork, a spoon-and-fork utensil. They can do this with you facing them or facing their back.

Also try: If your mate is limber, lift their left leg up to increase the depth of penetration.

Hot tip for her: From the Spork position, have them lift their top leg and support it by resting it on your shoulder. From here, they can easily stimulate their clitoris using their fingers while you're inside them."</string>



    <string name="pos_40" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Horny Mantis

Benefits: Relaxing position with deeper penetration and increased intimacy.

Technique: Both of you lie on your sides facing one another. Your partner bends and spreads their legs, and angles their vagina toward you. You lift your legs between theirs to enter while they wrap their legs around your back.

Also try: They can use their legs and feet to pull you close during thrusts for deeper penetration."</string>



    <string name="pos_41" formatted="true">"Also known as: Sidewinder

Benefits: A very intimate face-to-face position that encourages hugging and kissing.

Technique: This is an ideal position if your partner is pregnant or either one of you had a knee injury because it keeps weight off the body. To get into the position, begin by lying on your sides and facing one another. Your partner spreads their legs slightly to allow you to enter them, then closes their legs so the part of your shaft that\'s outside can press against their clitoris. It's easy to kiss from this intimate face-to-face position.

Also try: Because thrusting is more difficult in this position, use different techniques such as grinding, circular, and up-and-down motions for added stimulation.

Hot tip: Hug eachother for 20 seconds before getting busy. Hugging raises your levels of oxytocin, a bonding hormone your body produces naturally, and that will enhance your connection."</string>


    <string name="pos_42" formatted="true">"Also known as: Crisscross

Benefits: Prolonged slow sex to build arousal. Shallow thrusts stimulate the nerve endings in the head of your penis.

Technique: Sit on the bed facing each other with legs forward. Lift your right leg over their left and they lift their right leg over your left. Come together so you can enter. Now both of you lie back, with your legs forming an X. Slow, leisurely gyrations replace thrusting.

Also try: Reach out and hold hands to pull together for pelvic thrusting. Also, take turns alternatively sitting up and lying back without changing the rhythm."</string>


    <string name="pos_43" formatted="true">"Also known as: Bottom\'s Up

Benefits: They gets a prime view of your derriere.

Technique: This is challenging: Your partner lies on their back while you straddle them facing away. They lift their legs and wrap them around your back to elevate their pelvis so you can enter. They then grab your butt to help you slide up and back. They can add a little massage action to their grip also.

Hot tip: Spin around into missionary style to face them while trying to stay inserted. Then switch positions, this time with them on top and facing away."</string>


    <string name="pos_44" formatted="true">"Also known as: Getting a Leg Up

Benefits: Quicker orgasms for your partner; easier motions.

Technique: From The Spider, your partner can lift their legs onto your shoulders, which increases the muscular tension that advances the orgasm sequence. By elevating their butt off the bed, it'll be easier for them to thrust and grind in circles."</string>


    <string name="pos_45" formatted="true">"Benefits: You both can still maintain eye contact while viewing the action at center stage.

Technique: Both of you are seated on the bed with legs toward one another, arms back to support yourselves. Now move together and they move onto you. Their hips will be between your spread legs, their knees bent and feet outside of your hips and flat on the bed. Now rock back and forth.

Also try: They grab your hands and pull themselves up into a squatting position while you lie back. Or you can remain seated upright and pull them against your chest into the Lazy Man position.

Hot tip: Help turn them on by straddling their bottom and massaging their back. While you're busy with your hands, they can wiggle, grind, and move their mons pubis in a circular motion against the sheets to stimulate the clitoris."</string>

    <string name="pos_46" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Face Sitter

Benefits: They can direct the position of your tongue and the pressure against them by rising up or pressing down.

Technique: Your partner straddles you placing their knees at your ears. They can hold onto a wall or headboard for support. While you\'re doing your thing, they can use their fingers to graze their nipples or rub the top of their vulva.

Also try: Hold your tongue firm as they gyrate their hips, pressing their clitoris against it."</string>

    <string name="pos_47" formatted="true">"Also known as: Inverted 69, Over and Under

Benefits: Simultaneous oral pleasure.

Technique: When they\'re on top in 69, they can control the intensity of oral stimulation on their clitoris by lifting or pressing their pelvis. From this position it\'s easy to work their finger magic on your perineum, the sensitive area just below your testicles. Also try the man-on-top position.

Also try: Roll over onto your sides in the 69 sex position.

Hot tip for her: Place a cup of warm tea and an ice cube on the nightstand near the bed. When they give you oral sex, they can alternate placing the ice cube then the tea in their mouth."</string>

    <string name="pos_48" formatted="true">"Also known as: Hovering Dragonfly

Benefits: A comfortable position for your partner. An erotic one for you.

Technique: Rest a pillow behind their head, then straddle their shoulders. Support yourself by holding the bed\'s headboard or the wall.

Hot tip for her: If your partner's mouth becomes dry after awhile, they can add some mint- or fruit-flavored lube to your shaft."</string>


    <string name="pos_49" formatted="true">"Also known as: The Bees Knees

Benefits: Great for out-of-bedroom fellatio.

Technique: Your partner kneels in front of you, covering their teeth with their lips and encircling your glans with their mouth. They then slowly piston their lips up and down on your shaft, alternating speeds and occasionally stopping to move their tongue over and around your head.

Also try: Lean a dressing mirror against a wall to the side of your body so you can enjoy the view of your partner going down on you from the side versus top down.

Hot tip for her: For variation, they can take one of your testicles into their mouth as they stroke the shaft with their hand."</string>


    <string name="pos_50" formatted="true">"Also known as: Romper Room

Benefits: See The Hot Seat. Also, adds bounce to your thrusts.

Technique: Have a ball in your workout room? Use a stability ball to add some bounce to The Hot Seat. Sit on the ball with your feet on the floor. Have your partner back up onto you, sitting between your legs. Roll and bounce to it. "</string>

    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-8127887406337874~7451623883</string>
    <string name="banner_unit_id">ca-app-pub-8127887406337874/2075174127</string>
    <string name="interstitial_unit_id">ca-app-pub-8127887406337874/8449010785</string>

</resources>
